Josh Burrows

www.joshuaburrows.com

936-933-6263

jburrowsdev@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Be a productive, reliable, loyal, and honest employee. My personal goals are to find a position within a goal-oriented business, and to become part of that team to progress the business interests, brand, and my personal skills as a developer. Leading construction projects both commercial and residential has given me experience in managing people and well as clients. Tracking different scopes of work, coordinating around scheduling conflicts, and seeing a project through to completion has taught me how to troubleshoot and make decisions. These traits have been beneficial to both my work and home life. My hope is that my experiences will continue to evolve as I improve my skills and qualifications. I'm always willing to learn something new and apply that knowledge to new situations. Please see my work experience below, and I appreciate the opportunity to be considered for a spot on your team.

EDUCATION

September 2017 Real Estate License, Angelina Community College

Associate of Arts degree from Angelina Community College

KEY SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JS, Git, GitHub, Node.js, Bootstrap, React.js, Libraries, API's

Decision making and problem solving

Works effectively with others, as well as, independently

Vast knowledge of hand tools, mechanical tools, and their applications

Delegating and time management

Organized and Self-motivated

EXPERIENCE

Feb 2013-Present

Owner- Josh Burrows Construction

Procuring jobs, managing construction process, scheduling, bidding, billing, and general management. Projects include: Project Manager of Naskila gaming at Alabama-Coushatta Indian reservation, Indian Hills Restaurant and Bar, Alabama-Coushatta education center, and general contractor of additional residential property, remodels, and new construction in and throughout Lake Livingston area.

June 2011-Feb 2013

Sales and Route Training Manager, Faust Distributing

Sale and deliver products to c-stores, grocery, and other points of sales. Train new drives of routes and expectations. Train sales personnel on company equipment and standards. Merchandise and rotate products

October 2007-June 2011

GPS SURVEYOR, GLS

Plotting points on grids for the seismic search of oil and minerals sub-surface. This was necessary for the exploration of resource deposits located underground. Mainly oil and natural gas exploration

ACTIVITIES

In my free time I enjoy being outdoors. My family is the most important thing in my life and any decision I make is based on their needs. Staying proactive, positive, and productive are ideas I strive to maintain. I believe its important for a person's self-worth and identity to adhere to those standards, and necessary to maintain a healthy and fulfilling lifestyle.